{
    "subject": "Abel_Gance",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Barberousse",
    "human_readable": "Abel Gance created Barberousse.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9269240498542786,
            "question": "What was Abel Gance's inspiration for making Barberousse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7566748857498169,
            "question": "Who created the film Barberousse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4946780502796173,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4690829813480377,
            "question": "What year was Barberousse released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43600940704345703,
            "question": "What is the plot of Barberousse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4185289442539215,
            "question": "How did Barberousse receive critical acclaim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3566056191921234,
            "question": "What genre is the film Barberousse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3507871627807617,
            "question": "Is Abel Gance a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3143375813961029,
            "question": "Who are some notable actors in Barberousse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17776194214820862,
            "question": "What other films has Abel Gance directed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abel Gance created Barberousse.",
            "html": "yago_4177_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some notable actors in Barberousse?",
            "html": "yago_4177_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Abel Gance a filmmaker?",
            "html": "yago_4177_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Barberousse?",
            "html": "yago_4177_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4177_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4177_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4177_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4177_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4177_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4177_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4177_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4177_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4177_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4177_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because the document contains a section titled \"Barberousse (1917)\" which clearly states that it is a silent French film directed by Abel Gance. The same information is also mentioned in other documents, but the query is answered positively only if all documents collectively confirm or deny the statement.\n\nSo, according to the context information provided, Abel Gance indeed created Barberousse, which confirms the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Abel Gance created Barberousse.\" Both files mention that Abel Gance directed a film titled \"Barberousse\" in 1917."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}